Child, you are walking in the garden of Eden.
You shall be tested.
I can't not do the voice when the fucking, you know, Talos principal music is here.
You gotta forgive me.
I can't not do that.
Yes, I love him.
I was not planning on streaming today.
So this one goes out for all you Americans.
I know the time zones aren't always perfect for you guys, so here we go.
I'm just really excited to play Isaac, okay?
Isaac was indeed calling, and I responded.
I heard the call, and I showed up.
Yeah, I have to be a little more quiet than usual today.
Just because I have neighbors and I don't want to be accidentally screaming, you know?
But we'll see.
I mean, I can't contain myself.
If I get too excited, you know, but I'll try to keep it in as much as I can.
We're gonna be super chill, yes.
You play Arc Raiders in your free time still?
I don't actually, but I was thinking of getting back into it.
Then I thought, man, everyone's probably so good nowadays.
I'm played in so long, you know?
I'll probably be fine.
There's matchmaking.
Should be okay.
I was thinking of getting back into Deadlock, actually.
That game is amazing.
Really want to play Deadlock.
I've not played Seafool.
Pick it drippy.
Hey, what's up, George?
Peak Streamer at the moment.
Thank you.
Appreciate it.
I want to get into Deadlock, but it seems complicated.
Yeah, I mean, I wouldn't say it's any more complicated than Dota or something like Valorant.
Yeah, it's probably a little more complicated than Valorant, but if you've played Dota before and you've played a shooter, it should be pretty simple to get into.
It's really, really good, yeah.
Valve quality game for sure.
I long for the day that Oliver loads up Escape from Tarkog.
Unfortunately for you, I've already tried it and I didn't enjoy it that much.
It was too overwhelming.
There was too much crap, man.
There was too much.
All the menus, all the freaking items, all the... I don't know.
It wasn't for me.
Also, there's too many good people there.
I'd probably just get my ass handed to me.
Arc Raiders was definitely more up my alley.
It was a bit more casual coded, which is perfect for me.
Tarkov may be a little too hardcore for me.
I think if I got over the initial hump of learning the game, I could find some enjoyment from it.
Because I do really enjoy games that have a deep simulation of certain things.
Like, I love Microsoft Flight Simulator, you know?
I love simulator games in general.
It's just a lot of fun.
I enjoy that type of thing, you know?
But it's always about getting past that initial hump of difficulty.
Make a crisp, tasty Coca-Cola.
Maybe I will.
Have you heard of the Don't Escape games?
I have not.
Unless you're talking about the bird's eye view, you're running around, there's a chicken Tarkov thing?
Isn't that a game that came out recently?
I saw that you added Risk of Rain to your backlog.
Would you consider changing that to Risk of Rain Returns?
Basically the same game, but it looks better and has more content.
Wait, are you talking about the first Risk of Rain?
Because yeah, sure.
I mean, for sure.
I did play Risk of Rain 2, but not that much.
It was super fun, actually.
I want to play that more.
Especially now that I've gotten more into roguelites lately.
I think I can find some more enjoyment out of that now.
What time is it in the US?
It depends where you live in the US.
Such a big country that people on the west and the east coast have completely different time zones.
2 p.m.
okay.
I can see myself playing some Risk of Rain 2 for sure.
I enjoyed the beginning of Terraria, but then I started not enjoying it very much and it became a pain and then I quit.
It was very fun in the beginning.
The very goals for today.
Nah, I'm just gonna have fun playing Isaac, man.
No goals at all.
Just chillax, you know?
Play some Isaac and get some wins.
Unlock new items, try new builds.
Dude, just saying this out loud gets me so excited right now.
We're going in.
Oh my god.
We gotta play Isaac.
I wonder if I should start off with a chat.
Oh, you know what?
Kinda want to do a speedrun, actually.
It's been a while.
Okay, here's the deal.
I'm gonna random.
If I get
Isaac, I'm just gonna make up some arbitrary rules here.
If I get Isaac, Cain, let me see.
Azazel or Eden, we're gonna do speedrun.
If not, we're not arbitrary and meaningless, but it's fun.
Why?
It's gotta be Judas.
Okay, not a speedrun then.
That's good, because speedrun with this guy is probably a death sentence.
Not a smart idea.
I'm scared.
Okay, we got him.
Like, as Judas, I feel like maybe I should be using my book every third room.
Like, maybe I should be using it here, you know?
You just use it.
I have so little HP anyway, might as well get the damage in.
I mean, if I'm gonna die anyway, right, might as well die having done all I could.
You know what I mean?
Got a coin.
No bombs, though.
Thank you, buddy.
Just ran into the fire for me.
Oh, we have a curse of the question mark.
I hate that curse.
I predict this is gonna be Ludovico.
Oh, man.
I don't even know if Ludovico can be in there.
Plus five bombs.
They stick to enemies and release slowing white creep puddles.
That is actually pretty good.
That is gonna make these bombs much easier to use against bosses and stuff.
I like it.
Money.
I have six bombs now, so I can definitely start to be a little liberal with that.
Question mark item for 10 and for 15.
Ooh, I don't know what that means.
Oh, actually, I think I do.
This means this is a trinket, right?
And this is a non-trinket.
I could be wrong.
Also, I'm gonna go back and get that chest down here.
There's also a key.
I'm gonna do it here, so I also have access to that heart later in case I need it.
During combat, dropping the trinket will cause mobs to stomp.
Like, is it a continuous stomp?
Because it seems completely useless, this item.
It's horrible.
If it's a continuous stomp, then maybe it's good.
I can put it somewhere in the center and just stay out of the sight, you know?
This is gonna be okay.
So wait, this could actually kill me.
If I get dealt down,
worth the shot.
If the run ends, it doesn't really matter.
We just started anyway, right?
Okay, two bombs left.
Three.
I'm gonna wait until this retrovision disappears.
It's not a good time to have retrovision.
No, fuck it, go.
It's Dingle, who cares?
I'm gonna smash him.
You gotta be... Okay, dude, the fucking fly blocked my bomb.
I was gonna put the bomb on the boss because it's a sticky bomb.
It was all planned out and everything.
The fucking fly fucked me.
I can't believe it.
Okay, that's just beginner unlock.
Wait, what is the block?
Isaac!
You know what that means?
Speed runtime.
Let's go fast.
Okay, wait, that's not fast.
We don't do that.
Cursed Eye charged shot that fires up to five tears.
Oh, you know what?
Ah, launches a ring of ten large tears each time Isaac takes damage.
Chance to also briefly gain the anemic.
You know what?
I'm not a big fan of that.
I'm gonna come back.
That's right.
Coming back for that.
I'm gonna be re-rolling like a madman.
Well, we can't really re-roll that much because we're also on a timer, right?
We're speedrunning.
Nice.
That's actually kind of huge.
What are you doing, sir?
Can we even get a full charge?
If we don't find a battery, I don't know if we can.
This may be impossible.
Good.
We got the boss.
I'm gonna wait with that.
Just a bit.
Now, I did say speedrun, but we have to clear to get the battery.
It's a must.
Hey, sir, come here.
This is gonna take a while.
A while I don't have.
Oh, man.
I took damage from running into him?
I didn't think that would happen.
Good stuff.
Let me go into this curse room.
Oh, shit.
Not good enough.
Pills.
Oh, shit.
Oh, boy.
That's bad.
It's gonna be an uphill battle now.
Let's see what we got in here.
I should probably buy that health.
I can't even afford it.
Shit.
Okay, well, this was not a great start.
I'll say that.
Blighted over him.
He's not that hard.
He's scary as hell, though, because he's so fast.
But he's not really difficult.
That was beautiful, wasn't it?
I don't like this one.
I like this one.
Good, good.
I'm gonna go back and grab the other item before we leave.
First floor definitely took longer than it should have, but it's okay.
I'm leaking.
So the question is, where do we go?
We have two keys.
I could go in here, actually.
Why not?
Let's see how much HP we actually have.
I think we have two hearts right now.
We lost one because we ate the pill, and it wasn't good for us.
It didn't agree with our tummy.
I still can't see my HP, dude.
Wait,
I can make it.
How did I... like how?
Oh my god.
I've never been more unlucky with pills in my life.
This is actually the worst start of all time.
Doesn't get worse than this one.
We gotta do this.
Isaac's fork.
What is that one?
Chance to heal half a red heart each time you clear a room.
Hey, that's not bad.
I like it.
How to jump?
Oh, or question mark.
Let me see.
This is pretty much essential, but that's gonna replace my active.
I can't do that.
No.
Analog stick.
Wait, what?
Ooh, we're mousing, baby.
We're using the mouse.
Let's see how this works.
Oh, that's awesome.
Dude, that's actually amazing.
Okay, this run is saved.
I just gotta... I've never used the mouse before, so bear with me here.
Wait, I can aim at anywhere.
That's crazy, dude.
Shit, let's go this way.
This way here.
Also, I gotta move my mouse pet over now, suddenly.
I need my mouse pet.
I mean, I'm just gonna sit here and aim.
Hey!
This is really weird, though, keeping track of... I'm not used to this at all.
Hit that guy.
Oh, man, this is actually kind of weird.
Good shit.
Oh, we don't have time for that.
Keep moving, keep moving.
Three coins?
That's not worth it.
Okay, we're done here, right?
Go.
The Rainmaker.
I'm gonna have a d6 for this.
I'm gonna have to sort of lead him a little bit when doing that.
Oh, this is actually kind of cool.
Oh, what's this?
Right.
I still can't hit anything, though.
Yeah, I gotta lead him a little bit with a... let's, like, rotate.
Dude, not bad at all.
Not bad at all.
I like this.
I'm not gonna take a deal.
I'm not.
Even though I have Reroll.
I'm gonna go Angels, because I don't have a lot of HP.
We're moving.
Can I see my HP finally?
Dude, what the fuck?
Three times in a row?
Oh,
good.
Am I gonna get hit?
Nice, we healed.
This way.
Dude, it feels so weird playing with a mouse.
It feels illegal.
I mean, it's nice, but it's definitely weird.
Come here.
What's that?
Mom's pearl, chance of... Yeah, you know what?
I like that more, I think.
Boss is here.
Why not?
Min Min.
I forget what you do.
Oh, shit.
Okay, I see.
Shoot little guys.
Oh, man.
It's gonna be a pain, isn't it?
How on earth?
Using bombs strategically?
Wow.
I used all my bombs.
The fuck is this?
Okay.
I can't hit him.
There we go.
Fuck yeah.
Thras!
It freezes fire rate from Isaac's left.
Yeah, I like that.
I'm gonna go in here.
Okay, listen, that's a good item, but the D6 is better.
I'm actually gonna re-roll it.
Wait, I bet I can take it, use it, switch back, and then re-roll.
I'll be taking that.
And I don't have a bomb, unfortunately.
So I can't go in here.
That's too bad.
We're on a... we got... we got to find a treasure room, though.
That is a must.
Hello?
That needs to happen.
I can't leave without the treasure room.
Are you crazy?
So it's probably down here, right?
I would imagine so.
No treasure room here.
Oh, there's... I don't know what to do here.
I don't have a bomb either, so fuck it.
So it is actually the big room.
That's so unlucky.
Hey, come here.
Get him, get him, get him.
Nice.
Oh my god.
Here it is, here it is.
Capricorn!
That's definitely taking that one.
Definitely.
No money, though, so fuck that.
Not going in there.
We're leaving.
Why do I look like... I don't even know what that is.
Mythical creature.
Are we ahead of the timer?
Let's see.
I think barely.
I need to hustle a bit more here.
North.
Oh, not this room.
You know what?
I'll come back.
I don't like that place.
Let's see what we... Okay, that's dead end.
Oh no.
Is that the first time I've ever done this room without taking damage?
I think it may be without being disabled, I mean, and being able to fly.
What do I currently have?
I like that one, actually.
I think I'll... We don't have time to destroy poops anyway.
Fuck it.
Oh god, what the fuck is this?
Dude, what the... What an evil room.
Wow.
I can't even get in there.
And wouldn't you know it, I went the complete wrong way here as well.
Ah, maybe.
Maybe not.
Jesus.
What?
I wish I could see my HP.
Dude, I can already foresee problems with this mouse control.
When there's gonna be a lot of shit on the screen, I will not be able to find my cursor.
This is gonna be a problem.
I can tell you right now.
Get back.
No, no, no.
Fuck, this is the complete wrong way we've been going here.
I should have gone north, man.
I should have trusted my initial instinct.
Dude, I may go back to the keyboard.
I don't know if I can play like this.
It is so awkward.
Here.
What the fuck is that?
A mushroom boy.
A blue one.
No.
Oh, fuck.
Re-roll that.
Contact damage to enemies.
Explosions leave behind fires against damaged enemies.
Okay.
Community to damaging fires is kind of... Oh, I shouldn't have done that, actually.
That was dumb.
I'm not gonna press the button.
We're just gonna leave.
Eight dollars?
We don't have time.
Go.
Found the boss as the last room.
It's crazy.
That is actually just very unlucky.
Dark one.
I'm gonna sit back here if you don't mind.
I'm gonna charge again.
What are you doing?
Okay.
That's speed.
Sure.
Yes, we'll do that.
Go.
I think we're on par with the timer here.
We need to get some luck with the room placements now.
I predict right.
Oh, man.
Oh, Jesus.
Yeah, I mean.
Brutal.
I like the prism effect, though.
That really helps against multiple enemies.
That was a shit room.
You're gonna charge me?
I'm just gonna try.
Come on.
Another dead end.
I'm in danger.
Oh, yeah.
I think... I think we may be fucked here.
I don't know how to beat these guys.
There's... there's too many.
Am I...
fucking hell!
I can't... I can't win.
I just can't do it, man.
What am I healing from?
Oh, wait.
I'm not.
They're healing?
Wait.
What the fuck is going on?
What is the shit room, man?
Blow them up.
Fuck all of y'all.
Wow, that was aggravating.
Fucking hell.
Oh, wait.
What?
How do... I can't play with the mouse.
I swear to god.
It's because of the mouse, guys.
That's my excuse.
I can't play with the mouse.
I just can't do it.
It feels so wrong.
Now, you would think it's amazing, right?
But it's not.
Oh, no.
Oh, shit.
Oh.
This is scary.
We got to go slow with this guy, for sure.
Okay, what do we got?
Is that a tooth?
A rotten tooth or something?
Either that or a cat.
No, dead tooth.
Firing creates an aura around Isaac that poisons enemies.
That's not bad, I guess.
I mean, it's kind of bad, but not.
Yeah, dude.
Sick.
Not bad.
More flies.
Get poison nerds.
Got to remember to poop everywhere we go.
Nice!
That's kind of big on this character.
Okay.
Famine.
Yeah, he's gonna do that, of course.
Kind of want to get in there and poison him a little bit.
There we go.
Oi!
Get poisoned.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I got hit by that bullshit.
No!
I was playing so well.
Horrible.
I'm not gonna try and get in.
Oh my god, really?
How?
Why is he not poisoned by that?
Oh my god.
We have half a heart, man.
Oh, and we get the bandages.
The worst fucking item in the game.
Oh, that is so rough.
Keep moving.
Huh?
Hold on a minute.
What's happening here?
Drus?
What the freak is this?
I mean, this is going to be a short one because I'm dead.
I can't survive this.
Looks to be some kind of, uh, I don't know, toxic version of...
well, what the other area was called.
I forgot the name now.
Oh, these are enemies.
Uh, sir, come here.
What is this?
Forever alone?
Uh,
gamble.
Depression!
I mean, that's what I'm suffering from right now.
Enemies that touch the cloud have a chance to be struck by a damaging light beam.
Sure.
That's fine.
At least I'm getting some flies here.
We have to play perfect, by the way, which means not going in there.
Oh, wow.
I don't want to waste my flies here.
That was a crazy range.
Uh, no bomb, unfortunately, and no key either.
Nevermind.
Got the key.
I'll set this way first.
Wait, what?
Oh, there's a modifier on the floor!
And there's poop pockets, too!
I don't know if I like that.
It's like a sewer.
That's what this is.
Oh, I can't heal.
That's right.
It's like the whole shtick with this guy.
Okay.
Come on, you.
Let me fly.
Oh, money!
Please, health up!
Yeah!
Sick.
We're back.
I wonder if I can touch these buckets.
I'm not even going to try, actually.
I'm too scared.
I don't think I'm allowed to.
I'm probably going to take damage.
Like, why would you touch a bucket of poop, right?
Uh, if I destroy this, can I still...
I can still get the fly.
Nice.
Even though it's on the other side.
Oh, what are these?
Oh, wow.
I got hit by something there.
Man, this is rough.
How on earth am I going to hit these guys?
Yeah, I mean, I could barely see those projectiles.
I'm not kidding.
That is rough.
Man, I am just getting my shit pushed way inside of my body right now.
It was outside at first and now it's all the way in.
But now it's time we reverse that.
The shit is coming out because we're speed running, baby.
That's right.
Azazel, my beloved, free me from this torment.
We just went from a...
or the worst character in the game to the best.
It's going to be quite the difference.
Of course, we get that Azazel luck.
Immediately we're rich.
Rich get richer in this game.
That means we're going to get a lot of money going now.
You're going to be doing that.
Yeah.
And you're dead.
Stapler.
That's good.
We like that one.
There's another boss.
Let's just go for it.
Steven.
Oh, that was a bit risky what I did there.
We also got a tidbit rock.
No, I got hit by that.
Crazy.
Let me see.
Oh my God.
Wait, if I take this, I die, right?
Wait, Blood Oath is actually good here.
That's Azazel at the start of each floor.
I don't have any red hearts, right?
So it's bonus damage speed for the rest of the floor.
The problem is though, if I don't have any red hearts, and this supposedly gives me damage for removing red hearts, I'm not going to get any damage from it.
Unless there is a baseline of if you don't have any red hearts, you get at least a little damage.
And then other red hearts after that give you damage, right?
Because it says the stat grants bonus damage and speed for the rest of the floor.
And then it says the more health sacrifices effect, the more stats it will provide, right?
So maybe there's a small bonus if there's no health, you know?
But it's not worth it.
I already lost one health.
Let's go back.
We got to find the treasure room at least.
Oh my God, Steven is fucking with my perception.
Just briefly though.
How did I miss that?
Also, there was a tinted rock in the boss room.
Show me the treasure.
Loving coins.
I mean, buying a blue heart here is actually worth, I think.
Yeah, it's worth.
I was considering the the coin thing for 10, but yeah, decided not to do it.
Nice.
Dude, I'm always so happy when I play this character.
I'm just loving life, you know?
It's great fun.
I kind of want to play the new character.
Apollyon.
Treasure room?
Where the fuck are you?
Oh, nice.
Look at this.
We got an eternal heart.
That is huge.
Sure.
We take it now.
It's fine.
This is the most elusive treasure room.
How is this first floor so big, by the way?
Like, what the hell?
Or is this the second floor?
I don't know.
Like, I don't remember.
Everything's flowing together, these runs here.
Wait, what?
There's two treasure.
What the fuck is going on?
Oh, wait, is it the XL?
I see.
Oh, two bosses, two treasure rooms.
Wait, we don't know what this is.
Mom's perfume.
Fear shot plus tear up.
Okay, cool.
What happens if I re-roll after taking an item?
I don't like this, man.
This is such a...
I'm trying to do this.
It's not gonna spawn a new one.
Worth a shot, though.
Um, here we go.
We can't waste any more time.
This was a good first floor, I think?
I think, yeah.
It's just because it was so big.
No, that was the second floor.
Fuck me.
Well, okay, then.
All right.
All right, then.
It's Truss!
Oh, the random tear effects.
Uh, I don't know what's gonna happen down here, but we're gonna see what's going... Oh, we got this weird thing.
Uh, I think I'll take this.
I take all the hearts I can get, man.
Oi, oi, oi.
Jira.
Sure.
Let me click this.
Okay, I mean, that button is just amazing.
Oh, look at that poop water coming in.
It's disgusting.
Another Jira?
We're gonna save this Jira until we find two black hearts at once.
Or two blue ones.
Hagalas.
Uh, maybe I'll use that.
Ugh.
Later.
Are you dead?
You're dead.
Little bloop!
What the fuck is that?
It looks like one of the sipper dudes.
Without the sipper.
Oh, yeah.
We got Angel, baby!
Uh, sure.
Just get out of here.
I'm actually gonna blow this guy up.
Huge.
Oh, no.
Oi, yo, yo.
I'm afraid of the fires.
Oh, you bastards are taking all my HP.
Who the hell is that?
Key piece two.
Nice.
We could move on right now, but we should really look for a treasure room.
I couldn't speak.
Also, I think, no, I was about to say right down here, but no, no, no.
Secret room.
Uh, okay, wait, if I blow this up, minus, uh, infinite luck.
So that's bad.
I don't know.
Maybe if I find the other key piece, we can do something there.
Nah, probably not, because that works on one door already.
Oish.
What happened to him?
Did he get stunned?
Hmm?
No, I got hit.
Wait, dagas?
Oops, dagas.
Okay, that's how you say that.
Uh, tinted rocks.
Oh, wait, speaking of tinted...
Oh, I forgot a tinted rock back on the last level somewhere.
Shitballs, BBF.
Can live that bounces around the room and explodes in context.
I don't like that.
Let's take this.
Sure.
Hot bombs, it is.
And that's it.
We leave.
Actually, wait, wait.
Right here, dude.
Right here.
Fuck!
Okay, well,
whatever.
We gotta hurry.
Uh, quick, take this.
Use it.
And go.
Just for fun.
Wasn't that fun?
I thought it was fun.
I'm gonna get in here.
Uh, uh,
saving the Jira for at least two blue or two black hearts.
This is the plan.
Or, I don't know, a million money or something.
Uh, we don't have time to go in there.
What a funny room.
There was a bomb there.
Oh, hot coals?
Or embers, I mean.
Oh, what the...
What am I taking damage for?
Oh, for spiders.
I did not even see that.
I was looking for the fucking worm.
All right, son.
You're gonna throw bombs at me.
Dude, he's taking so much damage from this laser.
Wow.
Holy fucking shit.
That damage is amazing.
That box, I like it.
Oh, fuck you.
Duplicate.
You motherfucker.
Okay.
And then we have this thing, pushpin, chance to fire tears that are piercing and spectral.
Uh, I already have that.
Yeah, I already have both of those, so fuck it.
I guess we'll take it, I guess.
The empress.
Which one was that?
More damage and some other stuff.
You know, that item is actually not bad on Azazel.
Coming in from behind and yeah, I'm taking it.
That's actually not bad at all.
Still no treasure room found.
We may not have time,
but I mean, we gotta do it.
Fast, fast, fast, fast, fast.
Now we're totally chilling on speed here.
Uh, I think I can take that.
Yep.
And we're gonna go for, uh, keep moving.
Go, go, go, go, go.
Speed is really good right now.
Wait, is it really up here?
I can't believe it.
It is, wow.
Wait, what is that one?
It looks like pyromaniac to me.
Fire mind?
Tears apply burning effect that damages enemies over time.
Chance for tears to explode on it?
Ooh, that means I need some more range.
Otherwise, this could get hairy.
Uh, yeah, I'm gonna quickly blow these up.
Just for fun.
And now we go.
Go, go, go, go, go.
This was decently fast floor, I would say.
All things considered.
Go.
I need to be at max range with this.
Otherwise, I think I'm gonna be in trouble.
This could realistically be very dangerous.
I'm so scared.
I don't want to be in here.
I forgot to look at the timer, by the way.
Okay.
Sure.
Good.
Oh, wait, I'm immune to the fire, right?
Hold on.
I'm immune to fire on the floor.
Uh, yeah.
Are these stationary?
I mean, they were moving just before they were stationary, so I don't know if that counts.
Let me try.
I am immune, nice.
Uh, kill this guy.
Thank you.
That bird, or I'm gonna take this.
Teleport 2.0.
This is an interesting one.
So, we go to square before we go to boss, and then we go to question mark, which is secret room.
Oh, notice how one of these question marks are like, white?
The other one is gray.
Okay.
Why?
Coins, treasure, step, dice.
Okay, uh, I'm gonna do it.
I'm just gonna straight up do it.
Okay.
Oh my god.
Get away from me.
Are you dead?
What's happening?
Okay, let's leave.
We're not doing great on the HP front here.
We could use more HP.
Question is, if I blow things up with my laser now, can I blow up, like, rocks?
I don't think so.
I think this way.
Watch me be wrong, and it's the other way.
Like always.
I just hurt myself.
That's how you speedrun.
Uh, blow it up.
Coins for me.
Great Gideon.
The all-knowing.
Okay, he doesn't take damage, it seems.
Uh, this is definitely like a hagala situation.
What's happening?
Oh, why are you not taking damage?
Oh, shit.
Oh my god.
Maybe it's gonna be weakened after we kill all the adds?
Huh?
Oh, three of six, huh?
Three of six waves?
Or...
Dude, I'm gonna die.
I don't know what's happening here.
This is, yeah, yeah, this is some crazy shit.
Whoa.
Half a heart.
Oh, man.
Ah, shit.
Dude, is it just me, or is this game, like, fucking hard all of a sudden?
Like, what is happening?
I can't even fucking get through three floors.
Ay!
Man, too bad.
That was close.
Lazarus.
He's a solid character.
I got no complaints with the las.
Good times are guaranteed.
I take it back.
Kill this guy.
Don't even think about it.
Hey, you.
Uh, okay.
I think I want a speedrun.
We have a good setup and layout for speedrun.
Oh, he's fast now.
He's fast now.
Good shit.
Wait, this is a double trouble.
It means there's another treasure room.
We're gonna go for the treasure room, then.
Oh my god.
I'm not gonna fall for your shenanigans.
Nerd.
Suck on it.
Oh, that's a great item to start things off, and we're gonna take this.
It's a good time to take this.
More tier.
Spectral tiers.
Yes.
Dude, another... this is two out of three conjoined, then.
I'm taking it.
We're going for conjoined.
Whatever that means.
No, wait.
I know what that means.
That means we're gonna shoot multiple shots.
That's good.
But wait, we're not leaving yet because, you know, treasure room.
There's another one somewhere.
It shall be mine.
I love these black ones.
I hate the red ones.
Black ones are my pals.
He's camouflaged.
Galus?
That means we don't take damage from stuff on the floor.
Which is awesome.
What the hell is that?
Safety scissors?
Diffuses troll bombs and converges them into... Hey!
Oh, that's actually kind of a tough choice.
Uh, oh, I would love both, honestly.
But, oh, backstabber again.
Now we leave.
Speed run.
We found two treasure rooms.
Life is good.
Oh, I don't even have a... okay, fine.
Jump down to hatch.
And no curse.
Lovely.
Dude, this little familiar that shoots tears is actually doing considerable damage here in the beginning, at least.
Like, no complaints here.
Diamonds was coins.
Okay, we're gonna save that until we have a bit more.
Sick.
Oh no, we have no key.
Key's paramount right now.
Appeal.
You know I eat those.
Range up, shot speed down.
That's... I think that's okay.
That's fine.
A little annoying.
Okay, shot speed is really down.
They weren't kidding.
It's not just a little bit, it's a lot.
Uh, still no key.
Oi!
Uh, we can take that now, actually.
Because we have a Blackheart as a buffer, and everything's cool.
Fuck you!
Buffer is very fast, disappearing right now.
Uh, I'm scared.
Boss is here.
Let's go.
Still no key, which is crazy.
Oh nice, we kept the elemental heart.
Fuck yeah.
Uh, I don't... I could go in here, actually.
Yo, we sacrificed these two bad boys.
Huh?
It's actually not a bad idea.
We go full sacrifice on this.
Ohoy!
Okay, so now...
Black powder?
What is that?
Spawns damaging penta... Ah, that's a bit weird.
Increase damage in size.
Shooting out fires will cause them to explode.
Contract from below decreases the likelihood of a... Dude, I hate both of these items.
This is the worst role of all time.
Holy shit.
I got fucked.
This was so unlucky.
What the hell?
I can't move on like this.
I need to get to that treasure room, at least.
Like, we need to find a key.
I refuse to do this.
Right, we can't even do that.
And again, this is, uh, you know, risking the elemental heart, uh, the, um...
Fuck is it called?
You know what I mean.
Uh, the heart.
It's eternal heart.
Eternal heart.
It's a risk we have to take.
Give
me a key, man.
Pentagram.
Well, they are my keys.
Lovely.
I could go in here as well.
And buy, uh... gabble.
Burp?
Hey.
Tears up.
Hey, I like that, actually.
I'm happy.
Yep, yep, yep.
And now we go get this room.
Sixty-nine?
Cancer.
HP up, plus you... What?
Three soul hearts.
After taking damage, all additional damage in the room is reduced to... Whoa!
That's pretty much like a wafer.
Poor man's wafer.
I like.
I'm so good.
Uh, this is not... Wait, what happened here?
Oh, destroying fires explodes shit, right.
That's a thing now.
I gotta be careful with that.
Uh, we gotta leave.
I think we're still on speedrunning, uh, schedule here.
We can do it.
It's fine.
We're cooking.
Almost tripped on that.
Go!
Caves.
Oh my god.
Damn, you're tanky.
Making them bleed feels good, though.
Making bleed.
There we go.
Just taking a look.
Okay, nothing.
Nothing interesting.
No curses either here.
We are doing well.
I feel like the, uh, the new areas I can access are actually kind of harder.
Come on.
Dude, suddenly I'm just showered with keys.
Do it.
No fear.
Shit!
This may have been a mistake with this guy in the room here.
This could have been an infinite, uh, bomb situation.
I like damage nullifying more, I think.
I'll be back with more bombs for you.
No, I'm not.
I'm on a speedrun.
I chose this damage here.
Yeah!
I had to do it.
Bleed!
Bleed.
Make a pentak ramp?
Oh, it's too big of a circle.
Okay, fine.
Yonk.
Dude, die.
Please die.
There we go.
Wait, I guess hitting flies from any angle considers back step or is considered a back step.
Suddenly, there's keys everywhere.
Gordi.
I'm playing it safe.
Oh, that actually kind of saved me a little bit.
Dude, that shield lasts a long time.
Was it 10 seconds or so?
Kind of nuts.
Ah, you're fast.
You're faster.
Oh, I get it now.
You can see which direction he's shooting by, where his head pops out.
That is so nice.
Oh, that makes this a lot more comfortable.
Glad.
Oh, nice.
I like that.
No treasure room found yet.
I gotta go back, man.
I gots to do it.
Ah, I can't leave without it.
I think we're on good pace here anyway.
We gotta find one more book and then we can shoot two tiers at once.
And we don't even need a million dollars for that.
Oh, my God, you're fast.
Let's make a little gram for you.
God, nevermind.
Infestation.
Be good to me.
Ah.
How does that even happen?
Yo.
Wait, I was invisible.
I guess it doesn't work when you're in a new room.
Thank you.
Well, we're Azazel-ing.
All roads lead to Azazel.
And boy, does it feel good.
Oh, there's an enemy.
It's like, let me in.
Uh, yeah.
I don't like spiders.
This was a triumph.
Watch this.
Boom, right there.
I was wrong.
It's okay.
Oh, it's probably north, actually, between the...
Yeah.
Oh, I didn't mean to... It's like, shit.
One bomb left.
Oh, no, I can't enter the room.
Oh.
That is just some cosmic fucking sadness right there.
That is amazing.
I can't believe that.
I forgot to look at the freaking timer again.
God, it feels good to have this item.
Oh, you're dead.
Okay.
Let's do it.
Get destroyed.
That's another tears up.
We're gonna be charging so fast.
Oh, that feels so good.
Oh, that's nice.
We need some more health, though.
This is like, the big thing.
Damage is good now.
Now, we need help.
This is a... Let me see.
We have to fight here to shrink enemies.
Shrunken enemies tend to flee and can be crushed.
I mean, why not?
No reason not to take it.
It's not, like, fantastic.
Oh, my God.
They are coming off screen so fast.
Paws is here.
This guy is actually so nice to attack when I have Brimstone.
Stapler.
Oh, God.
I can't actually go in there.
Oh, I can't go in there either, man.
I'm gonna... I have no HP.
We gotta go.
His speed is calling and we're barely ahead of the timer.
We need to hustle ass now.
Oh, that was risky.
That could have been really bad.
What the fuck is that?
Oh.
No, I want this.
Sure.
Good.
Turn these off.
What the hell is that?
Bag launch.
Five percent chance when taking damage to destroy the trinket and spawn the lunch item.
It's actually not a bad idea.
Except, you know, the other trinket is really good.
But getting the lunch item could be really nice.
We really don't have time for this, so I'm just gonna blow everything up.
Except, no.
You, man.
Fuck you.
You better give me a good item.
Give me.
I am anger.
I am pure anger.
Turn right.
What the frick?
Why are they so small?
Oh, it's this shit item I have that turned them small.
It's actually not good, because then I can't see them.
That was nice.
I smell poop.
Teleport to the...
oh.
Ah, but wait, wait, wait, wait.
But there's no angel chance, so fuck, right?
We're fucked.
Double coins?
Just do it.
What the?
Okay.
Ah, eeee!
Shit.
And we get this shitty item as well.
One heart is looking bad.
Uh, homing tears.
Yeah!
That is actually massive.
We gotta, uh, we gotta go.
That was great.
We really need to not take damage now, so we can get some usage out of this act of...
This is the main deal now.
Bra?
Uh, no.
It's just not worth it.
Four hands!
Jesus.
I'm scared of this.
I'm not even gonna go in there.
Nope.
I don't, I don't trust like that.
No, it's a fake shop!
I was hoping for a blue heart.
Oh, this is an awkward room for mom.
More?
What the fuck was that?
I'm not sure what just happened.
Give me items?
Okay.
I keep thinking I can fly.
Every time I have a laser, I'm like, oh yeah, I'm a Zazel.
But no.
Ice sink!
We need to really be precise here.
Oh, it's one of those aggressive situations, I think.
Or not.
Oh, fuck you!
Yeah, there we go, there we go, there we go.
Good shit, good shit.
Uh, where are we going today?
Are we taking... Okay, so wait a minute.
So I don't think this, whatever this strange door is, we haven't opened this yet.
The only strange door I can think of is the door where we need the key.
That we have already done, right?
So this is like a different thing.
I just don't know what's happening, so it says can be used to open a strange door.
But I don't know if that door is like in the deeper stages.
And this strange door is a different strange door in the higher stages.
I'm gonna assume that it is.
So I'm just gonna take this because it's damaged.
There's damage on it.
Oh, we gotta go here.
Fuck.
We're actually in time.
Um, what the hell?
There's a new item.
Fires, lasers, scissors?
Loosier, head?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, hold on.
Icek's head detaches, remains... No.
That's horrible!
Fucking shit item!
I want my Bible!
That was the worst choice I could have made, but of course I couldn't have known.
That's just how the cookie crumbles sometimes.
Oh yeah, I'm ready to stay at range here.
We gotta play Space Invaders.
Absolutely.
Use this.
Okay, he's angry now.
You're dead.
Wasn't there another one?
You.
I think we may be okay here.
Our damage is just too good, you know?
It's gonna be nice.
Oh, fuck you then.
You gonna come from the left now or something?
Is that a weird Steven?
Who's that?
Steven's long dog's brother.
He's using the... Dude, the Bible is incredible.
They pretty much saved everything.
Like, this is what makes this run right now.
Oh, I'm taking that.
Get him out
of here.
Wasn't there a guy up here?
Yeah, there you are.
Dude, we're just blasting through these stages here.
12 out of 15 already.
Holy shit.
That came from off screen.
That felt good.
Oh, what the... There it is!
We got the lunch!
Now we can throw away the trinket.
It's angel time.
Who's next?
That's 15 out of 15.
We have done it.
A giant cell.
Sure.
Well, that was nice.
Okay, let's go.
Moving on.
It's time for the utero.
Apparently, I can walk on those when they're small.
Not that I need to.
We don't have time to do that.
We got to keep moving.
I say north.
Nice.
Part spawned.
No problem.
Get away from me.
Wait, what's that?
Oh, he's camouflaged.
That's what's happening.
Oh, this room is awkward for this.
Dude, we have full HP.
How crazy is that?
I'm even going to go in here, because why not?
At this point, I mean, first I... No, thanks.
Invest this.
Hey, I like it.
Good shit.
No boss yet.
Fight room.
Wait a minute.
So this is going to lead me down here.
It's probably here, isn't it?
Here's the Bible.
Oh, interesting.
Oh, you bastard.
Temperance.
I forgot what that was.
So what is two?
Hold on.
What did I write?
I can't see it.
There it is.
We don't know what it is.
We don't know what it is, so we're going to take it.
What happened?
This is the same.
Uh, I don't know.
No clue.
Here we go.
The damage is crazy.
Shovel.
Uh, no, I'm definitely going anywhere else.
What is this?
Boo.
I mean, sure.
I'll take it.
We're done here.
I can't, I can't take the shovel, man.
I need the, I need the Bible.
What is this?
Pinky eye?
You have to fire poison tears.
Uh, yeah.
Empty chest or what?
Okay.
Nothing in there.
So many moms here.
Oh, the spiders.
With all this money.
Um, I don't know.
I don't have time for this.
We're just going to do that.
Fill this guy up.
Feels good, man.
I keep thinking I can fly.
What is Temperance?
Lot donation, right?
Wait, what?
Oh, it's up here.
I mean, this run is going pretty well.
I think it's going to be a good chance I'll be able to kill whoever is in my way for this run.
I really need to fuck this up to lose, you know?
Like, it needs to be some catastrophic failures.
You're dead.
No, you're not.
Man, where's this boss at?
Come on.
I ain't got all day.
I think I know where it is now.
It can only be one place.
No, I can't.
Oh, I could also be in the top left, please.
Don't do that to me.
Fuck me, man.
Insanity.
This may be GG.
I'm not even going the right way.
Come on, faster.
Go.
Open.
And of course, I chose the dead end right here of all the fucking places to go.
Go.
It leaves.
Oh, my.
The damage is actually out of control.
Wow.
Demon.
Guppy's head, pentagram, that one for sure.
Nope.
I'm not taking that.
We are going to go down deeper stages.
Oh, I keep thinking that guy that's following me is a little enemy, but it's not.
I think we were too slow, by the way.
I can't remember whether or not it's after it lives or it's the Satan thing.
We get to fight the other guy.
You ain't nothing.
Keep moving fast.
Find me that boss and find me that boss now.
Nope.
Actually, yes.
Real quick.
Okay, whatever.
Unlucky.
And there's the boss.
That was fast.
Satan.
You did it.
I'm going to bomb you now.
I managed to do it once.
Here come the feet.
Good.
Okay, so I wonder if this portal on the floor qualifies as the mysterious or secret door or whatever.
I don't know.
I don't think so.
Could be.
Oh, okay.
So we got to look for a door now.
I don't think we can go deeper than this.
That's not true.
I think we can we can go deeper.
Maybe with a shovel.
Go this way.
He wants coins.
I don't care about that.
That
was nice.
Line him up.
Oh, you know what?
Maybe the secret, what is it called?
Is it called secret door?
Wait a minute.
Strange door.
Maybe the strange door is the red door with the crack in it.
I forgot where exactly I saw that, but there is also that, right?
That one I haven't opened yet.
Could be a... Oh, we're actually kind of fast here.
Mama Gurdi?
That's a new boss.
But you're dead.
Oh, okay.
You weren't anything to write home about.
Even Gurdi's mama wasn't anything.
Yeah.
Get me in there.
Yes.
Wait, did I?
Oh, oh, right.
This is the one with all the bosses.
Right.
Or second, I was like, wait, what's happening here?
The lamb.
Here's the book.
He has a bit more HP.
No problem.
Oh, no.
Wait, what is this on the floor?
Kill it.
Supper.
Okay.
Fuck.
Why is that one faster than the other one?
So weird.
Skolex.
Oh, it's this one.
Wait, Benji, that's not the same as the last one I had.
Is it?
Was it all future pedestal items to rotate?
Oh, it is.
I could have sworn this was called something else.
Okay.
Also, we've had it before, but I guess we had it in greed.
Wait,
do I even need money at this point?
I don't think so.
Show me more bosses.
Yeah, I love the experimental pills.
That's okay with me.
I needed a bit more speed.
I am kind of slow.
Not even at one speed right now.
Burp.
Good.
That's fine with me, too.
That's really good.
Like a shurn.
That was an easy room.
So the boss in here, that's gonna fuck our shit.
It's gonna be a delirium.
We gotta be ready for that.
Could have it at any moment.
Oh, shit.
Ah, we're fine.
Wait, is that snot?
No.
Okay, too bad.
I was hoping it was.
Wait, what happened there?
Don't take my battery.
I mean, I don't have any battery, but still, don't take it.
Where the boss is at?
Bam, bam, bam, bam.
I mean, it's almost like I'm speedrunning this level here.
Damn it.
I was being a little cheeky there.
I admit it.
Mr. Fret.
Well, he's gonna die.
I'm gonna kill his children.
Like the weirdest boss ever.
I think I'd rather take this.
I feel like there's not a lot of bosses on this map.
Usually, there's like a million bosses.
Dang it.
There's still a couple areas here.
This could lead to a big area with a bunch of bosses, I guess.
Ah, that goddamn poop.
Let's supper again.
Ah, it's less speed.
Plus one lock, though.
Another dead end.
Like, I've cleared everything?
Is it really in the last room?
Okay, there's a couple rooms.
No, thanks.
Okay, there's a boss on the right.
That's probably it.
Or it ain't.
There's also one here.
Could be the one.
We have a lot of hearts now.
This is a very ideal situation.
It is him.
Here we go.
Where are you?
Oh, there you are.
We're gonna play Space Invaders here, for sure.
Oh, goddamn, that was bad.
Kill this little guy.
Angels.
Kill this guy.
Ah, get away from me.
Dude, he's fast.
What the fuck?
How do we even dodge that?
Oh, I walked on creep.
I should have kept my, uh, my feet.
What they found early on.
Oh, my God.
It's not going well.
I'm losing the arms race.
I'm too slow, man.
My move speed is just not up to par.
We gotta kill him fast.
Stay at range, stay at range.
Get that damage in there.
Look at all my little armies here.
Yeah, I think that's it, baby.
Another W.
On Delirium.
We don't need to watch that.
We know what happened.
Compound Fracture has appeared.
Can't wait to have that.
Compound Fracture feels good.
Okay, let's switch it up a bit.
I want to do challenge.
That was a nice run.
The next one is Beans.
Chili Beans, I hope.
Are you sure you want me to die?
What the fuck is this?
Butt bombs, explosions, damage, and concuss all enemies.
All right.
Ninety-nine bombs.
Nine, nine, nine, six, bomb burn.
The Black Bean.
Upon taking damage, Isaac releases several farts to damage, poison, and pushback enemies.
And we also have the Bean.
It releases a fart that poisons enemies and deflects projectiles.
And nine bolts.
There's just one charge bar after active item use.
So that means we have infinite farts.
Items with a one-room recharge become an automatic timed recharge.
I mean, this is...
I mean, look at that.
Infinite farting.
And lots of bombs.
Wait, we can't shoot!
Oh, crap!
Oh, boy.
That changes the game.
We need to poison and bomb them, I guess.
Is this the strategy?
That's actually hilarious.
Hey, sir.
All right.
Let me in.
Ace of Spades.
Peace has a finding a card.
Sure.
This will do that.
Bam, bam.
Should I be bombing these fires?
I guess I should.
Ah, that was kind of a waste.
I'm gonna bomb this guy.
Oh, my god.
This is an interesting challenge.
And I think I like it.
Yeah, this is great.
I need to... This is a good time to practice my bomb juggling.
Oh, I can't juggle my bombs!
Well, shit.
Wait, these guys can't be poisoned or...
Beautiful shot there.
Well, that's useless for me.
Range is kind of... I was about to say no treasure room, but we're doing a challenge.
So, yeah, there are no treasure rooms.
Okay.
Kill all these guys.
Honestly, this is not that bad.
Like, I have good damage.
This is solid.
And it pushes away the projectiles as well, dude, is actually so cool.
Spiderbot!
Oh, we're definitely getting that.
I know we can get the money for it.
I need it.
Basically, spacebar is now an offensive button and also a defensive one.
Oh, look at this.
Oh, we're definitely blowing these up, though.
What's up, dude?
This is actually amazing.
It's already one of my favorite challenges.
Oh, this is gonna be so nice.
He's not gonna have any chance.
Wait, I didn't poison him?
There we go.
Screw!
Oh, did we take a deal?
You know what?
Let's go for angels.
I forgot I wanted to buy the item just as I jumped down.
Fuck me, Spiderbot rip.
It's okay.
I don't need it.
Let's open the door there.
Hey, cool.
No fucking way.
That was very unnecessary.
Didn't need to take damage from that.
That's very unnecessary here.
It happens.
I guess it protected me against those guys.
There we go.
Please die, please die.
Oh, wait,
the bombs?
Hold on a minute now.
They concussed the enemies.
Oh, that actually is very helpful.
How am I gonna deal with these guys, though?
Do I have range for this?
Wait, how can I deal with these guys?
Maybe if I deflect the projectiles back at them?
Yeah, that's how.
I... huge blunder.
I thought my charge was ready.
We lost the demon or angel, I guess.
It it farts through rocks as well.
That's actually kind of big.
Good fart.
Pestilence.
This guy likes bombs, huh?
Oh, fuck.
What is that?
Why am I dying?
I don't understand how it took so much damage.
Not this item.
Ah, man.
I gotta go to the shop.
Give me money.
Hey, sick.
Now, what is this one?
Diplopia duplicates old pickups and items?
I can't do it.
I need my fart.
But I can do it in here.
And then, you know, two beans.
That's kind of exciting.
The empress or the empress.
No, this is the chariot.
Chariot is gonna give me some damage, right?
Yeah, I think I would rather have that.
And then the key, of course.
I'm happy.
Wait, I could also take the battery and...
Wait, where's the item that I just had?
What?
Diplopia.
Did it get consumed?
They must have gotten consumed.
All right.
I was like, let me recharge it and duplicate again, you know.
Time to do some more farting.
Hold on, Sip.
Okay.
Go!
Why the hell not?
I thought I said juggernaut.
Spawn a beggar.
What is this room?
Dude, not only do you poison them, you also attack them with that, because the projectiles fall back on them.
This fart is really good.
I love the fart.
If you time it right, you can actually do crazy things with it.
I'm actually gonna go in here.
Too bad.
I could go grab that heart, but not yet.
Now it's worth to go back and grab it.
Oh, there's one.
You're dead.
Yeah.
Must be one stinky fart, though, to have things literally die from it.
There we go.
And you're dead.
Dude, this may be... I'm not gonna say my favorite challenge, but maybe my favorite challenge.
It is just that good.
Greed.
Oh, wait.
I can't push the bombs.
That's for you.
Wait a minute.
Why?
Oh, we have a curse going on right now.
Nice.
Oh, not this.
I'm getting pretty good at this.
No problem.
Ooh, Vistula is gonna be nice with my fart.
It all went away from it.
Whoa, the Concussive Effect has a very large radius on that.
You saw that?
Get away from me.
That was nice.
Chance of Planetariums.
Nice.
Why not?
What's that?
Uh, I'm gonna save my... Hold on.
What was in that shop?
Was there anything else I wanted to buy for 15 coins?
That should be something, right?
Ah, it was empty.
Damn.
I still think we have a chance to get another shop.
Oh, is it gonna be uterus now?
It could be, actually.
No, it's not.
It's not.
Oh, that's nice.
Extra speed is very needed.
Okay,
bomb them.
The fact that the concussion or concussion has such a big range means I should be using it anytime I enter a boss arena, like anywhere.
It doesn't matter.
Strength, I like.
Oh my god, that's a rough one.
Oh, fuck.
Angel chances are reducing.
Dodge that.
Wait, bomb them.
So silly, man.
Such inventive challenges, I will say.
Like, how do you even come up with this, you know?
Yeah, you know what?
Let's bomb them.
That's a hagalas.
I can see it, by the way it is.
Please die, thank you.
No, it's a chira?
Uh, oh, soul hearts.
Watch this.
Not too shabby, eh?
Get blown up, nerds.
Damn it.
He dodged that one.
Come on.
No problem.
I really don't want to deal with you.
Gotta use the bombs to get in there.
Oh no!
Actually, we have plenty of HP.
We got this one in the bag.
The boss fight is going to be interesting, though.
Oh my god.
I actually got black hold into that.
They got me good.
I can feel my damage is falling off, though.
Show me what we got.
Oh wait, adjustment.
I was about to say I have 69 keys, but no, that's bombs.
What's this?
Oh, the sun!
I didn't need to buy the bomb.
What am I doing?
That was a waste.
I will take this, though.
Go!
Float.
Bomb for you?
I can't believe that.
Again!
What a little fucker.
I can't even get close.
Oh my god.
Wait, I just realized how to manipulate the bombs.
We fart them into him.
Dude!
That's how you do it.
Oh my god.
Insane tech discovered.
That's a useless item for me, unfortunately.
All my black hearts are ripped.
It is what it is.
Okay, here we go.
100% angel mode.
That almost went bad.
Safety!
That was a little risky.
Oh shit.
Dude, how am I...
Like, how do you do this without taking damage?
It's impossible, man.
It's impossible.
This room was insane.
That was...
My fucking game is all tapped!
That was happening!
What the fuck is going on?
Uh, oh wait, I can see it now.
Uh, uh, options.
Fucking fuck...
What the fuck?
How did that happen?
Where am I?
Dude, that was unfair!
Fuck that, man.
Jesus.
Holy shit, I must have pressed the keybind.
Wait, why can't I...
Oh, there's an enemy.
That just gave me so much stress.
Secret room teleport, and then we have this guy.
Plus one lock, chance to add an additional pickup to chests.
Yeah, I mean...
I think I like that more than the one I have.
Take me.
Um, okay, so let me try this now.
What is the fucking point with this machine?
Blow it up?
It makes no sense!
Whatever.
Okay, nice.
Uh, I think I want to go to the right, actually.
Honestly, I'm ready to fight, Mom.
I think I have what it takes.
Uh, the sun, of course.
Beautiful.
Wow, that bomb has a huge range on the small spiders.
Oh, here we go.
Except I can't get in there.
Yes, I can, watch.
Okay, okay.
Yeah!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Almost.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, my God.
Fuck you, then.
I don't want you anyway.
That was annoying.
Are you not affected by my fart, or what?
Okay, there we go.
Disgusting toenail.
Oh, my God.
I didn't mean to do that.
I meant to use space first.
I misclicked that.
Mistakes were made.
Why am I even doing this?
One black heart.
Hey, look at that.
Please give me a lot of hearts.
Crap.
Oh, that killed him.
Ice tears.
That's actually a upgrade for me.
Because if I freeze them, then it's easy to bomb them, right?
And somehow I still take damage, because I'm an absolute dumbass.
Just kill them.
Two of clubs, double the bombs.
Hey, that's good for me.
Give me some more ammo.
Solid.
They should be dying, right?
Uh, oh, we got the money.
Nothing to spend it on.
Whatever, just go, man.
Angel dreams are gone.
You gonna die from that, Mom?
You are.
Okay, wish me luck.
This is it, this is it.
She fucking pushed the bomb into me!
Nah, bro, this is just unfair.
I mean, nah, nah.
Nah.
Just fuck off.
Oh my gosh.
Fucking clutch the shit out of that, baby!
I locked the fucking at the end there, guys.
I really did.
I, man, I locked in.
Let's do one more.
This is good.
One more.
Unimas, Unimas.
It's in the cards, let me guess.
Card carrying nerd, or what's happening here?
We got the lovers, that's hearts.
And then we have this, what's happening here?
We have starter deck.
You can hold two cards at once.
All future pill drops are replaced with cards.
And spawns a random card on pickup.
So that's the one we just got.
Runs a random card.
Nine volts, that's more battery.
Allows active items to store up to two charges.
Alrighty, okay.
The tower.
Interesting, we can shoot, we can shoot.
That's something.
I'm not used to that.
I think I'm gonna for sure use that.
We got death.
And we have lovers.
And the tower.
I think I'm gonna replace the lovers with tower for now.
Yeah, I have no battery anyway, guys.
Just get away from me.
I used it all.
They met.
Man, that run was actually so epic.
I was so sure it's gonna die at the end.
I got so tilted when mom pushed the bomb into me.
When I thought I was gonna be clever and put the bomb on her, you know?
That really tilted me.
And then I was like, okay.
There's no reason to be mad now.
All you can do is lock in.
Fuck yeah!
The doors have opened, baby.
All of them.
But only on this floor, I think.
Okay, that's for later.
How did I not take damage there?
I was so close.
Nice!
I'm gonna use the tower in there, by the way.
I'm gonna fuck him up.
Oi!
Sick!
Actually, let's use it here, then.
Ah, wait, wait, wait.
No, we're just gonna use a normal bomb here.
Do it here.
In case there's a secret.
Actually, yeah, here.
Aw.
It was so good, though, wasn't it?
Until it wasn't?
Wait, more cards?
That's gotta be, like, hard-coded, right?
There's no chance.
Fifteen, though.
I don't have money for that.
Maybe this means all the cards are good now, and there's no bad cards, you know?
Because we have this...
I'm taking that now.
I feel confident, guys.
I don't need to come back.
Watch.
We're gonna use the tower.
He's gonna have a bad time.
It's the headless horseman.
Hell yeah.
No problem.
Come on.
Oof.
That was close.
He's going for seconds.
That was clean as hell.
A pony!
Point five speed, dash across the screen.
Isaac is invulnerable and deals contact damage while dashing, grants flight while health.
Increases speed to one point.
I mean, that's a no-brainer, I think.
We are literally flying.
That's good.
Even though this is the card character, I think this is worth.
Down, down, down, down.
Oh my god.
Oh yeah, we can fly now.
Let me actually try this.
Sick.
You!
Oh my god, dude.
This thing slaps.
Also, to the rock.
Uh, I got no bombs, though.
Magician... yeah.
That's good.
I'm gonna use this active against the boss here.
Uh, yeah.
Bam, bam, bam.
Gimme me!
I'm gonna line him up first.
If I can.
Uh, I mean, that was... that wasn't great.
This guy isn't that hard, though.
That's good.
Why are some of my shots so, uh, I don't know.
They don't shoot very far.
I need to get him into one of those stages where he can't get to me and I can sort of just cheese him.
You gotta hit him like not... like here, like that.
That's perfect.
See that?
That's the way you get the damage in.
I'll take that.
And that.
We're definitely going for demon.
Generates creep.
Orbital knife familiar that deals heavy contact damage.
I'm more interested in the blocking enemy shots, honestly.
I'll take both.
I think I'm happy with both.
Uh, we could move on.
But that's probably a bad idea.
We haven't explored much.
What do
we got here?
AWOS.
Oh, I like AWOS.
It's my favorite one.
AWOS.
Um, let me see what's in here.
Okay.
Let's look for a decoration.
I don't believe in any of these.
Ah, that was a misclick.
Let's use this.
I have to remember, this is my creep, not his.
The high priestess?
Do we see a decoration in here?
I don't... I'm not convinced, man.
None of these are convincing.
I mean...
I think it's worth getting just for the one out of three on Bookworm.
Oh, it also gives Seraphine.
It gives two.
Oh, that one is interesting, too.
But I can't afford both.
I think I'm taking this just to do that, you know?
If I take the Bible, it's like a guaranteed kill on Mother, though, which is like the whole idea here, right?
We get in there and we fuck her up.
Just one button and she's dead.
It could be worth it, but I think, honestly, the journey there is going to be more difficult, right?
Whatever.
Yeah, let's just move on.
Oh, I can fly.
I keep avoiding these rocks.
I could do speedrun.
Does that even make sense in a challenge?
Maybe it's like...
You get an extra reward, you know, if you do it.
Actually kind of satisfying to do that.
And we immediately have power again.
Owned.
Gimme.
Fight room?
You know, why not?
Oh, I don't even have a key.
Jesus Christ.
I forgot to use AWAS as well.
I still haven't found the decoration that I trust.
Did I see something in here?
No.
This is not good enough for me.
None of these are like clear at all.
Come on, that was awesome.
Come on now.
He nearly hit me.
Where are you?
We're gonna line him up.
Ah, almost had them all in one go.
One key acquired.
Could go into there, but you know what?
Let's do it.
That is one cheap card.
What's that?
Fully recharges the health active, response to the four random battery pickups.
Nah.
I think in the spirit of the challenge, why not?
Or death.
I think I would rather have strength.
Okay, do we have a decoration?
None of these look like decorations to me, man.
Oh God.
Dude, what the fuck is this?
This is insane.
This was like a boss.
Wait, I'm gonna wait for this.
Give me that.
I'm happy with it.
Lord decoration where you be.
Maybe, nah, none of this looks like it.
Maybe in here.
This one, I think.
Yeah, good job.
The spoon.
Homing tears.
That's very good.
And it's not even a trinket.
I always think that's a trinket, but it's not.
Uh, okay.
Wait, why does it say there's a...
Oh, I'm in the wrong spot.
I know where to go.
Just keep going down now.
Too bad.
There's actually no reason not to do this every room.
Homing tears, so good.
Let's do it, Gertie Jr. I'm gonna wait until he spawns a little guy.
Like that.
I'm gonna wait for him to line up.
Oh, you gotta be kidding me.
No way.
That was a bit unlucky.
Hey, cool.
Hey, not that...
Oh.
Took out the fire.
So, now I wonder if his tears or his lasers are always gonna be diagonal now.
We saw him do it once.
Really tried to dodge that.
Head of Krampus.
Why is a brimstone laser attack in all four cardinal directions?
Nah, I'm good.
I don't need this.
I like my current pony.
Catacombs.
There we go.
These things are so disgusting.
Why did I do that?
I don't even have...
Dude, I've been lacking keys so much this run.
It's actually disgusting.
There's a key.
I may save it, but there's like a room I really want to do.
Thank you.
I mean, this is just great.
This active slaps.
Line them up.
Yeah.
I will say, like, all of these challenges are freaking amazing.
I love them.
Maybe the solar system is a little questionable.
At first, though, it was still fun, you know, but...
God, damn, is that one hard.
Definitely the hardest challenge so far.
Is that my second steam sail?
Oh, look at this.
Massive.
No.
These guys look like they can't take damage, like you need to kill something else in the room, and then they deactivate.
Here we go.
Wait, I thought it would be mom by now.
I miscounted.
Homing tears are helping so much.
Now it's mom stage, though, right?
No.
Wow, I really thought we were at the end already.
I was totally off base.
At least deactivate.
Fuck, you still hit me, unbelievable.
Damage is good, honestly.
Just my tears itself is solid.
Wait, I wonder.
Not bad.
Perth row.
All right.
But do I wanna... what do I wanna keep?
Wait, I have this one?
I didn't realize.
Hell of a bunch of the secret room!
Oh, we even have a way out of here.
Amazing.
I guess we walk around.
No.
Okay, fine.
Bomb it.
Wait, I thought I had my active!
Dude, I just...
I ran into him because I thought I had it.
Shit.
If you don't kill enemies, you're not gonna get any energy.
At least we get the hearts back.
More tears, that's massive.
That is actually a significant upgrade.
Look at that.
Huge.
Here we go.
Do I want this black heart when Isaac is used to half a heart?
I think so.
We have enough bombs.
Wish me luck against the Haunt.
Double trouble.
Ohoy!
This may have been a mistake.
Yeah, we'll see.
And the homing tears are nice here.
One down.
I mean, that's just solid right there.
Health as well.
Nice.
No demons.
Now it's time to slap mom.
Sir.
Okay, my damage is falling off a little bit.
Thank god it's the last stage.
What the fuck was that?
I aimed that so bad.
That's on me.
Terrible performance there.
Wait, who's alive?
You're alive.
Unbelievable.
I can't get enough of that.
Arcade.
Uh, we can blow up some shit.
So, wait, what is the deal with this again?
Kill them all.
Rich, of course.
Now line them up and go.
That was a solid charge.
Uh, this way.
I could go in there.
I'm not gonna.
Ooh, let's see.
Two of hearts.
Honestly, I don't even need this money at this point.
Just fucking around.
Give me the boss.
I'm ready.
I am so ready.
Oh, we're gonna line them up.
Look, come here.
All of them are gonna come over here.
Oh, you asshole.
Here we go.
Mom, it's time to die.
Gotta scratch my nose.
Focus up, focus up.
Oh, nice.
Okay, try to blow her up.
I don't think it's worth it to play with bombs.
Maybe a bit.
If I do predictive bombing.
Ah, a little too early on that.
That was good.
You hit her.
The prediction came true.
Prediction.
Easy.
I'm also gonna grab it.
This, why not?
Money equals power, baby.
Yeah.
Not...
Superfan has appeared.
Very good.
Let me see now.
Man, I want number eight and eleven.
Next one is slow roll.
I'm scared of these.
Wait, there's green challenges too.
Back ass works.
April's Fool.
Pokeman's.
Ultra Hard Pong.
Scatman?
That sounds fitting for this game.
And I can't go further down.
I wonder how many there are.
Have a heart.
Brains.
Pride Day.
Onan Street.
The Guardian.
I can't even sort of imagine what these are gonna be about.
This one, I think, could be...
All the levels are just massive.
Like, we're talking 10x the size of a normal level.
And that's the difficulty, you know?
That the levels are just huge.
This one could be...
That you have to do the challenge in a certain amount of time, otherwise you lose.
So this is like the ultimate assasal test.
Without assasal, I imagine.
Blue Bomber could be...
That's an interesting one.
Maybe you spawn as the blue guy with one HP and you can only use bombs, which is dangerous because one bomb and you're dead.
Pay to play could mean that every single upgrade you find costs money.
So if you don't find money, you're fucked.
This one could mean...
Let me see, have a heart.
You can only find red hearts.
Or something.
Brains.
No idea.
Pride Day.
You're a lesbian.
Onan Streak.
I don't know.
It's Onan and he's on a streak or he's out there naked, running across the field.
Who knows?
The Guardian could be...
Oh, you know what this could be?
You have a familiar that you spawned with, but you can't let the familiar take any damage at any time.
You have to protect him.
You have to bring him to the end without him taking any damage.
Dude, that sounds crazy.
Imagine if that's true.
Wow.
April's Fool, no idea what that is.
Back Asswords?
Oh, is it gonna be...
You walk right, but character goes left?
Because that would fuck my brain.
Pokemans, no idea.
Ultra hard.
Maybe the game is just really difficult.
Pong.
Maybe every single projectile you shoot is gonna bounce off the wall and it hits yourself.
It can deal damage to you.
Scatman, it's poop, baby.
It's just poop.
Bloody Mary, you get drunk.
That's my predictions for those challenges.
Well, that was good.
Normal runs today did not really yield any meaningful results.
Except one of them.
But challenges came in clutch there.
That was actually so much fun.
The challenges came in, man.
I love shit.
I like that atmosphere.
I'm glad you do.
Otherwise, you would hate this game, I think.
Just bringing some calming music.
You got sun card on the fart challenge.
Your clutch was awesome but unnecessary.
Oh my god.
I wish you didn't have said that to me.
That's...
You know what?
I was...
I knew I had it.
I was making a statement, okay?
All the doubters out there.
This was for you.
I hope you like that.
Imagine I actually am like a secret Isaac professional and all of this has been a ruse since day one, you know?
Like off the top, like amazing acting.
Everything was pre-planned with a team of experts.
Like there's people...
I'm not even playing.
It's just someone next to me.
Like an actual...
I'm just sitting here saying shit, you know?
And then, oh, we should totally plan this, you know?
You get to one and then you have the sun and you're not gonna use it and...
That would be so much fun.
Ain't no way too much planning?
I don't know, man.
It's...
Probably you couldn't plan that because the game is randomized, right?
You couldn't say, okay, this run we're gonna have.
This run we're gonna have like a sun card here.
Unless you mod it.
Maybe you could.
Please do 8 SAZL runs next time.
I mean, I could do that.
I can do that easily.
And I would have fun.
But the thing is, I don't want to do the same challenge, so to speak, on the same character, right?
So if there's characters where I haven't beaten X-Boss, I want to do that, you know?
If I've beaten X-Boss on one character, and gotten the little, you know, check mark or whatever, I'd rather just do it on another character, just to get progress done, you know?
Please do 76 blue boy runs.
I have a disease.
Man, that's just pain.
I don't know if I want to do...
Why 76 though?
Why not 67?
How long has it been since the last Isaac run?
Today.
So like one and a half hours.
Or one hour even.
I did that today, it didn't go well.
I think I executed myself in a weird fashion.
It is a good question.
76 is the new meme number.
Oh, I didn't get the memo, sorry.
I'm not as up to date on the memes as you guys.
Even though I do follow the meme channel, I actually look in there quite often.
There's some funny stuff.
One of the best ones that I've seen yet in that channel, this is probably my favorite of all time, is the meme from Breaking Bad with Walter White.
He's out there in the desert on his phone, you know, looking all distraught.
And the text is like...
It's like a caption that says me when I'm in a humbleness competition and my friend...
I forgot what it was, but there's this weird music playing and it was just...
I was laughing for like half an hour watching that.
I couldn't stop watching it.
Oh, it was like me when I'm in a kindness competition and my friend lets me win or something, doesn't even show up and let me win.
You know, and he's just standing on his phone like his life just ended.
It's the funniest shit.
Who comes up with that stuff?
God damn.
Yeah, that's the one.
Me when I'm in a humbleness competition and my friend doesn't show up to let me win.
Something like that, yeah.
And there's this weird like bizarre music playing at the same...
It's just fucking weird.
An assault on the senses in all the right ways to make a laugh happen.
That's what memes are if you think about it.
Palicado, that depends.
It just depends on whether or not I will still have fun playing the game at that time.
Most likely I'll just try and figure it out myself and if I don't figure it out, it's just...
It's fine.
No biggie, no skin off my nose.
But maybe, maybe we'll do that.
If I'm in the situation where I really do not make any progress anymore, but I still want to play the game, maybe I'll do it then.
You know?
But I don't know if that's gonna happen.
We'll see.
This is an ad to make you join the Discord server.
Yeah, it is actually.
I will say, man, if I end up getting cancelled one day, promise me one thing, guys.
Let's say I become irrelevant and my streaming career is over and all of this is gone.
You gotta promise me one thing.
Keep the server running, man, because that is a great community we've made.
You know?
Like, if nothing else, we did that.
And I think it's so cool.
Like, this community is amazing.
So I like to think even after I'm gone, I have made people make friends, you know?
Like, other people have come together and they're having fun talking and playing games together and playing Minecraft on the server and all that.
I think that's so cool.
You're a nice guy, so you won't get cancelled?
That's what all the nice guys said before they got cancelled.
No, that's what all the cancelled guys...
I can't even say what I want to say.
Never mind.
I don't know why I talk about getting cancelled so much lately.
It's not that I have this ultra crazy secret that's coming out soon.
No, I'm kidding.
It gets cancelled all the time for rage-baiting on Isaac.
What did you do?
I didn't do anything.
I mean, I'm definitely guilty of some bait-maxing and people are not happy with that, but it's unintentional.
Like, it sometimes really does feel like I'm getting sort of cancelled for the rage bait that I'm doing.
And it's not on purpose, even.
It's like I'm being jailed, even though I'm not guilty.
Oh, that secret...
Yeah, that's pretty bad.
Yeah, definitely.
Let's just say I don't wanna...
I'm not even gonna make that joke.
That's too much.
Maybe that's too soon.
When are you gonna play Minecraft?
I really enjoy watching it.
Let me think.
I wanna say this year...
This year, we're gonna do...
90% chance we're gonna do Minecraft Season 3 this year.
Definitely not 2027.
That's too late.
So, before that...
I can see that happening.
But it depends.
Like, if I get the Minecraft itch next month, then obviously we're gonna play Minecraft in next month.
But if I don't get the itch, then I'm not gonna do it, right?
But the itch has slowly been building up.
I'll say that.
Taking a break from the game has definitely helped me, getting motivation back to playing it.
I've had a couple of times where I was like, hmm, should I play a bit of Minecraft off stream, you know?
Because I felt like just chilling with some podcasts or something and building whatever.
Then I thought, nah, you know what?
You gotta save that energy, you know?
Save that for when you start Season 3.
So, I didn't do it.
I've been putting it off.
I think that's better.
You're gonna play Isaac until the end of the year?
I mean, I hope not.
But maybe I hope so?
I mean, if I'm having as much fun with it, then I guess I'll love it.
But if I end up with like five viewers on it, I also have to consider that, right?
It's a balance.
Because in the end, this is like my job now, right?
So, it's gotta be like...
The best of both worlds is when I'm enjoying it fully and you guys are enjoying it fully.
That's like, that's the sweet spot.
I only care about money.
It's true.
Why do you think I'm doing so many streams lately?
You know, it's the end of the month, man.
I gotta make ends meet.
Oh, wait, it's not even close to end.
Oh, shit, okay, fine.
I admit it.
I'm addicted to Isaac, okay!
I admit it!
Ha ha ha ha!
By the way, are there people here right now that wouldn't have been here normally?
Because you're an American.
And you can't catch the usual streams.
I feel like I still see a bunch of the same people in chat, though.
Ergosphere?
Okay, okay.
I'm new here.
Hi, what's up?
Burger QE?
Burger Key?
Yeah, this is a better time for me in Canada.
Okay.
I like your name.
I'm usually at work, but now you caught me off of work.
I see.
You don't watch me at work, do you now?
That's not good.
I bet you start the game okay?
You're probably already ahead of me or something.
Dude, I kinda wanna...
At some point, what I'm gonna do, I'm gonna start a new save.
And just see how far I can go without dying once.
But this is, like, far in the future.
We're talking when I'm a fucking expert.
Like, when I am an expert at this game, I think that could be really fun to try.
Because the game does get harder over time, right?
So I wonder if I should start a new save file.
Am I just gonna fucking wreck everything?
Is it just gonna be, like, easy mode?
Or am I just imagining, you know?
So that could be fun to try.
Palicado?
Probably.
There's always some crazy people out there who are so good at games that it boggles the mind.
Think of the guy who beat all of the Souls games, Elden Ring, and Sekiro without dying once.
Actually, without even getting hit once, I think it was.
Hitless all games in a row.
How the fuck do you even get to that stage, man?
Right?
We excited for Subnautica 2 tomorrow?
I'm excited to see what people are saying about it.
I'm not gonna play it until it's out of early access.
But I am excited about the idea that is coming out tomorrow, and a lot of people are gonna have fun with it.
That's what I'm excited about.
Ascended autism?
Hmm.
Are you excited for Isaac 2?
There is no Isaac 2 full fungo.
Why are you filling my brain with lies?
There's a guy with a 4000 plus Eden win streak?
Why Eden?
Wait, how do you even do that?
I thought you couldn't play Eden forever.
I mean, I'm picturing that scene from American Psycho now with the business cards.
The guy saying, yeah, but what about...
Have you tried doing it with the blue boy, you know?
If you're good enough, Eden is infinite.
Oh, wait, do you get a token when you win with Eden?
Huh.
For some reason, I thought you could only get by playing other characters, but that's kind of cool, I guess.
I don't know why I assumed that.
Yeah, okay, when you win in general, okay.
I mean, you gotta be on some next level shit if you have 4000 wins in a row.
I mean, how is that even possible?
You must know everything there is to know about the binding of Isaac.
Some seeds are impossible?
Really?
You mean like, you can get softlocked or something?
Because it's not impossible as long as you can shoot, right?
I didn't actually know that the creator of Isaac made Super Meat Boy.
Is that true, though?
Like, was that only him who made Super Meat Boy?
Or was it also someone else?
Was it, like, multiple people on that and he was one of them?
Or was it also a solo project?
It's like the 13th time you've been told, isn't it?
I don't know, honestly.
Maybe second time.
I just seem to remember someone saying that...
Or saying these exact words and then someone else corrected him and then said, no, no, no, he wasn't the main guy on it.
Like, he was just there as a publisher or something?
Well, it could be just misremembering that.
Wikipedia says, he and the...
And one other guy.
Well, there you go.
There it is.
Yeah.
So, I wasn't...
I wasn't off base with that.
In fact, Edmond and Notch is the same person.
That's a lie.
What is Notch even doing nowadays?
Is he just chilling in his mansion?
Is he even making any games?
When is Minecraft 2 coming?
Why is nobody asking that question?
Being rich.
Can you play R.L.
Craft?
No, I think I'm gonna play the other one.
What is the name?
Create.
And you can't really mix the two, right?
It's like a whole different thing.
You don't think that's gonna be a Minecraft 2?
I think I'm gonna end up doing a...
Oh, I don't know.
Like, I don't know much about mods in Minecraft.
But as far as I understand it, Create is like a really big mod.
You know?
Where you may not even need, like, other mods.
Like, that is enough in itself.
What's this music?
It's from the Talos Principle.
A great puzzle game.
I really recommend it.
Fantastic music as well.
Create has so many add-ons.
Oh, you mean, like, other...
Yeah, other people made add-ons for the mod, right?
But the Create in itself is fine, right?
You don't need to have, like, a billion mods for it to be good.
I assume it's good on its own.
And if you have, like, a million extra mods, it's just gonna complicate things, and...
It's probably gonna be super overwhelming in itself, just to have Create installed.
The add-ons are cool.
I mean, I will look into that, of course.
Maybe I'll do, like, a mod pack with it.
Maybe not.
We'll see.
Hot take.
I'm not a fan of most add-ons.
I honestly agree with you, G-Game.
And this is not just for Minecraft in general.
I generally don't play, like, games with mods.
It's just not a big thing for me at all.
I enjoy the vanilla experience all the way.
So this is, like, me stepping out of my comfort zone with that.
Because in my experience, most mods, even though they are super popular and everyone's playing them, they're just not up to par, man, of the vanilla game, usually.
You know, you can tell it's made by an amateur and it doesn't fit with the rest of the game.
You can tell it's just janky as hell.
That's been my experience with most mods in games.
It's like, if you go to Nexus mods for...
What is it, Fallout or something?
Half the mods are, like, half-naked women with faces that look like...
Like, they don't even fit into the world and they have all these stars and the hearts, like, everyone's downloading them.
Like, why are you downloading this?
What the fuck is this, man?
I would never do that.
It's like ruining the whole vibe, the original creators.
Intended.
Because men, I mean, if you really want to get off, you know, there's other ways of doing it.
That involve, I don't know.
Maybe I'm just too vanilla for that.
I don't know.
But that's me.
That's just me.
I understand I'm definitely in the minority with that.
I also understand that mods are super important to keep a game going as well.
You know, like, some games are still being played today solely because of mod support.
So it is a good thing overall.
I'm not saying mods are bad.
It's just that I have a preference for playing the vanilla experience, you know?
Did you install the mod that turns Isaac into diarite?
Now I'm interested.
Now we're talking.
Where can I get this mod?
There would just be this cube floating around.
Repentance started as an Isaac mod that was made official.
Well, see, there you go.
That's awesome.
It's like Counter-Strike.
Counter-Strike was a mod as well.
And what else?
DOTA was a mod originally, and then they made a game out of it.
Like, a bunch of things, right?
I think Plants versus Zombies or something, like, in general, all these tower defense games.
It's also, like, originally mods, no?
And the auto-battlers, I have never played an auto-battle, but that's also a mod, right?
That was originally a mod.
So, mods are net positive for sure, like, definitely.
The concept for Factorio was born from Minecraft mods.
Really?
Damn, that really puts it into perspective how old Minecraft is.
Phew.
Man.
That game is old.
It came out in 2011, right?
Or, 2001?
2009 or something?
No, wait, how old is Minecraft?
Minecraft 1.0.
Like, let me see here.
At least days.
Yeah, 2011, November 18th.
Wow.
That's 1.0.
Dude, that is, like...
What is that?
17 years ago?
Yeah, the stream is over, Svarios.
And we're just... shooting the shit right now.
Stop, stop, stop, I know, right?
I can't believe it.
Pistons and horses were mods originally, huh?
I mean, modders have some of the greatest ideas.
Modders are essentially always passion projects, right?
Which means people are making those mods because they think it's fun.
And that the game mode they're making or the stuff they're adding is fun.
That's, like, the main motivation behind it.
It's not a monetary incentive.
It is what is fun to play.
You know, so obviously all the good stuff comes from mods.
Makes so much sense.
Yeah, I heard that story, Fartar, with Bethesda.
Like, they started charging for mods and everyone went crazy about it.
And they... and they revoked that thing so fast.
But now they're apparently bringing it back or something?
Yeah, Horse Armor, that's the one.
That was such a dumb move.
Can't believe they would do that.
Like, it's obvious not... it's obviously not gonna work.
What were they thinking?
Ark has paid mods now, and it's awful.
There's a paid mod for...
Uh, what's the game?
I'm blanking on that now.
Kerbal Space Program.
But it's, like, a really good mod, as far as I understand.
You know, the atmosphere or the clouds or whatever.
It's kind of... it's kind of messed up that that is, like, a paid mod.
But it's also apparently so good, you know?
It's crazy.
Did you play Grease some day?
You know what, I... I think I have that on my list.
I have been excited about Gris or Grease ever since Ezekiel III was talking about it.
Yeah, it is on my list.
It's in my backlog.
I was watching...
dropped frames with HitMeJP, Ezekiel, and Co-Carnage.
And Ezekiel was talking about this game called Grease.
And he was, like, enamored with it, you know?
But he also plays all these weird games.
He has this sort of, like, indie sundae, I think he calls it, where he just plays a bunch of random shit, you know?
Like, every week.
So he's playing a lot of stuff.
And he says this one is great.
Yeah, it's pronounced Grease, right?
Or what?
It's funny, in Danish, G-R-I-S means pig.
Like, straight up, pork, you know?
Grease.
Maybe that's how you say it.
I don't know.
It's your favorite game, Ella?
Damn, that's high praise.
Of all the games in the world, this is your favorite game.
That right there is high praise.
It's a short one, right?
I may actually throw a game like that in there.
Pretty soon.
Schweindebersling, Schweineminsch.
And I lost all my German accents.
Like, I used to be indistinguishable from a native German speaker when I was younger.
But I just never speak it, so...
This doesn't sound good anymore.
See, there's a game called Lorde.
I did see that.
I don't know what it's about, but I was laughing about it.
I don't think the developers realized what it's called, or what it means in Danish.
It straight up just means poop, or shit, in Danish.
I have not played Talos 2 yet, okay.
I'm excited for it.
Hope the music is as good as the music was in the first.
And the general vibe around it.
It's a game about Lorde.
Well, you just described Isaac.
Okay, guys, I'm gonna go...
I'm actually... I'm gonna go to bed, because I am falling asleep here.
It is quite late where I live, so thank you all for watching.
And I'll see you on the flipside, or whatever you say.
Bye-bye!